Daniel Guevara

Montreal,QC 4850 Chemin de la côte des neiges dgv1616@gmail.com

Profile:

I bring expertise across a spectrum of industries, encompassing marketing, education, construction, architecture, interactive technology, and natural gas energy. I have been in charge of creating and overseeing the production of a wide range of digital assets. This includes web pages, web applications, web components, REST APIs, and database systems for software applications. Furthermore, I am well-versed in crafting TDD-tested code, ensuring robust and reliable solutions throughout the development process.

Experience:

Full Stack Web Developer / Back-End

IVN Labs 03/2020 - present

Plan, create, execute, and integrate front-end and back-end components into web applications

- · Database management (create, read, write, update and delete information from Databases, tables and field)
- Creation, modification and deletion of IT web applications, Models, Controllers, Views and databases
- · Create Test driven development files to ensure the correct implementation of code in the developments
- · Integration of APIs

Full Stack Web Developer / Back-End

IVN Studios 06/2016 - 02/2020

Full stack Web developer creating the front-end and back-end of apps

- · Database management (create, read, write, update and delete information from Databases, tables and field)
- · Creation, modification and deletion of IT web applications, Models, Controllers, Views, databases, etc
- Web Design Experience
- Server management

Full Stack Web Developer

University Manuela Beltran

02/2014 - 03/2016

Full stack Web developer creating the front-end and back-end of educational web applications.

- · Make web design, hypermedia and web products, Create E-Material in HTML, CSS, Javascript and PHP
- Managing Rest APIs databases connected to educational software
- · Create content for virtual education Saas. Educational Remote experience of learning

Front End developer

Natual Gas Energy

01/2013 - 12/2013

• Create web pages with industrial designs made in 3D softwares

Graphic Designer

Edubooks - Full time

06/2011 - 01/2013

· Design educational infographics, flyers, and images for html content

Work by contract

Front-End Developer - Graphic Designer - Full time

04/2007 - 06/2011

- As freelance I work for clients as designer and as front end developer, creating their projects as requested
- Web developments HTML CSS Javascript language development

Programmer technical skills: Blade (HTML), Tailwind (CSS), JSON REST APIs, Laravel Framework, C#, Javascript, PHP Language, Visual Scripting Unreal Engine, TDD / Test Driven Development, OOP / Object-oriented programming, Perforce P4V, Git, GitHub / version controller

Code Showcase Link

Designer technical skills:

- · Photoshop, Illustrator adobe
- 3D Max Autodesk Vray
- Unity 3D program
- After Effects (motion graphics)
- · Multimedia content creator
- · Audition adobe
- Adobe's Creative Apps suit
- · Interactive Media

- UX/UI Web Design Experience Figma
- · Pixel perfect development
- · Concept designer
- Creativity and idea exploration
- 2D and 3D designer
- Branding
- Design Software
- · Very sharp eye for details

Education:

LCI LaSalle College International

Technologist in Computer Graphics, Animation, Multimedia and Web Apps Development.

WES Certification, Badge report Canadian equivalency: Diploma (three years)

Institute PDC

PHP Web Applications Development Certificate

Laracasts Active since 2019

Web App Education

Harvard University Currently Coursing

Major CS50's Computer Science

Skills:

Spanish - Native | English - Advanced | French - Basic

IELTS - Certification

- · Leadership and teamwork, the ability to manage and delegate to others and take on responsibility on the tasks
- Detail oriented, well organized and continuously praised for outstanding performance.
- · Communication, Social person with ideas to share and learn from others
- · Driven by results and success. Reliable and dependable
- Problem solving for design, apps and web developments
- · Commercial awareness Organisational Awareness
- Experience working with Startups and new projects from scratch

Daniel Guevara

Technician in Computer Graphics and Web App Development

03/2009 - 06/2012

WES Certifications